# **Curriculum Vitae**

## **Table of Contents:**

- >> Table of contents
- >> Contact information
- >> Profile
- >> Skills
- >> Education
- >> Work experience
- >> Languages

### **Contact information:**

Name: Beau Jean van Bemmel

**Title:** Web developer **Nationality:** Dutch **Birthdate:** May 9th, 2003

Personal e-mail: <a href="mailto:beauvanbemmel@live.nl">beauvanbemmel@live.nl</a>

**School e-mail:** 97085143@st.deltion.nl [preferred for business inquiries]

**Mobile:** (+31) 0636295096

#### **Profile:**

My name is Beau Jean van Bemmel and I am a software development student at Deltion College in Zwolle. I mostly focus on back-end web development using PHP and making CLI applications using Go. Perfectionistic but flexibel, experienced with SCRUM and a quick learner.

## **Skills:**



# **Education:**

#### Software Developer

Deltion College [08/2021 - Current]

MBO 4

#### **Curriculum:**

- HTML & CSS
- Javascript
- PHP
- MySQL
- LinuxSecurity
- Dienstverlening & Zorg

Landstede MBO [08/2020 - 07/2021]

MBO 1

## Curriculum:

- Dutch
- Math
- Civics

# **Work experience:**

# • IT Assistant / Janitor [internship]

Landstede MBO [12/2020 - 07/2021]

#### **Activities:**

- Assisting teachers & students with IT-related problems
- Installing new computers within our network
- Cleaning & maintaining hallways & classrooms
- Enforcing rules

## QA Assistant [internship]

ICT-Kringloop Zwolle [08/2020 - 12/2020]

#### **Activities:**

- Testing secondhand keyboards, mice, monitors, speakers
- Cleaning secondhand keyboards, mice, monitors, PSUs

## Languages:

	Reading	Writing	Speaking
Dutch	Native	Advanced	Native
English	Advanced	Advanced	Intermediate
Japanese	Beginner	Beginner	Beginner